Ed Bader's up for reelection.
Ed Bader要竞选连任
You know how he got to be mayor?
你知道他为什么能做市长吗?
You wanted him to be.
你想让他做
You're going to work at his office.
你去他办公室上班
All I require is that you keep your eyes and ears open.
我要你留神听留神看
I spoke to Rothstein.
我跟Rothstein谈过了
Masseria squeezed him out of the heroin business.
Masseria把他挤出了毒品生意
I should like to meet with Mr. Masseria.
我想见见Masseria先生
Petrucelli's the biggest importer of heroin in the whole southeast.
Petrucelli是整个东南最大的毒枭
Go back to Tampa.
回塔帕去
Those trucks he send up here with the rum...
他派过来装着朗姆酒的那些卡车...
maybe they carry something for us, too.
或许也能为我们带点东西
- Say hello to Abe Redstone. - Pleasure to make--
- 和Abe Restone问好 - 很高兴...
I will thank you in advance for your discretion.
我会提前感谢你的推荐
I'm assuming a reciprocal arrangement would be to your advantage?
我想一份互惠协议可能让你满意?
- It would. - Then until next time.
- 能 - 那么再会
Mr. White is alive,
White先生还活着
and you have crushed me.
而你背叛了我
Let me see you, girl.
让我看看你 乖
Stand up. Stand your ass up!
起来 给老子起来!
Think about what comes out of your mouth next
话说出口前要三思
unless you are ready for a war that you will fight alone.
除非你打定主意孤军作战
We're agents of the Bureau of Investigation.
我们是调查局的警探
Bring us your brother along with the criminals he conspires with.
帮我们拿下你老哥和他犯下的罪证
And your son stays a free man.
你儿子就不会坐牢
and you get to hold on to what matters.
同时你也可以掌控大权
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 大西洋帝国 第四季第10集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 大西洋帝国 第四季第10集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：Lee
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：沙漠玫瑰 潘P 校对：风花减减减 时间轴：Lee
I don't know exactly his position, but he's bigtime over there.
我不知道他到底算老几 不过他在那边很有名
- This is Balanchuk? - Yeah.
- 是Balanchuk吗? - 嗯
And you've dealt with him directly in Atlantic City?
你在大西洋直接听命于他?
Once or twice when he was Torrio's runner. I don't know.
他给Torrio跑腿时有一两次 我不很清楚
You don't know?
你不清楚?
Not since he got bumped up.
他升职以后我就不知道了
Joseph Balanchuk. What is that, Polish?
Joseph Balanchuk 那是什么 波兰语?
- It's Ukrainian. - I thought Torrio only worked with Italians.
- 是乌克兰语 - 我以为Torrio只和意大利人共事
- Does he? - It's a syndicate, for Christ's sake.
- 是吗? - 拜托 那是个联合财团
- Consisting of? - Italians, sure.
- 都包括? - 当然有意大利人
All kinds of greaseballs.
各种外国佬
Jews.
犹太人
He's got this one, Jake Guzik, runs his breweries.
他有个叫Jake Guzik的 负责他的酿酒厂
But this Balanchuk, he's high up the ladder?
而这个Balanchuk 他是高层?
Very high.
相当高层
He's like Torrio's second.
像是Torrio的副手
- Bring it up here, will you? - Right, boss.
- 把他带来 你行吗? - 遵命 老大
- Hungry? - My dad was a sea dog.
- 饿了? - 我爸是老水手
Tattoo of a mermaid on his forearm.
胳膊上有个美人鱼纹身
See the world.
放眼世界
I bet that sounds pretty good to you right now.
我猜你现在感觉特别好
I know this is difficult.
我知道这事不容易
But what you're doing takes courage.
而你做的事得靠胆略
You're a good father.
你是个好父亲
Tampa
塔帕
Get that. Come on. Let's get that unloaded.
接过来 快点 我们卸货
Let's go.
我们走
They ain't gonna move themselves.
它们可不会自己长腿跑过来
Come on, let's just give me a hand over here.
快点 过来搭把手
Give me another barrel of them oranges here.
这边再来一桶橘子
- Go. We're done. - All right.
- 走 我们好了 - 好
- Almost there. - How many more crates left?
- 马上来 - 还剩下多少箱?
- Just a few. - You still here?
- 剩一点 - 你还没走?
Ain't a mirage, lady.
正是如此 女士
Those trucks got to be on the road in half an hour, McCoy.
那些卡车再有半小时就得上路了 McCoy
I'm at sea for three weeks. Just catching up with the boys.
我在海上漂了3个星期 不过是和伙计们套交情
That sort of look like a woman.
那看着像是个女人啊
In the right light, I suppose.
只要光线恰当 我想也是
How would you pole jockeys know what a woman looks like?
你们波兰佬怎么知道女人长什么样?
Last call's over. Move your asses.
要收工了 动作快点
You two still got them full boxes here to load.
你两个给他们拿够装货的箱子
Let's go. Come on, get 'em out.
快去 速度 快点搬
He'd sweat his balls off in there.
他在那儿大概会汗如雨下
Should make Joe happy.
会让Joe高兴的
Tell him to come down next time.
告诉他下次再来
Let's move it along. I'm on a schedule, fellas.
动作快点 我赶时间 诸位
Keep an eye on these finocchi.
盯着这些货
Caught one of them trying to steal some of our hooch.
曾发现他们有人要偷我们的酒
You were supposed to call me three hours ago.
三小时前你就该打给我了
- You miss me? - Aw, shucks.
- 想我了? 呀呸!
This is business, which runs on a schedule.
这是公事 按进度运行的
You call me just to say hello.
你打给我就为问个好
Is that what this is?
就为这事?
No. Something's wrong.
不是 事有不对
Nuck, I'm hanging up now.
Nuck 我要挂了
What is it?
怎么了?
I said I'm hanging up. I wasn't talking to you!
- 我说我要挂了 - 我不是和你说话!
So what's the problem? Tell me.
是什么事? 告诉我
That wop you're in bed with, Petrucelli--
跟你在一条绳上的那个意大利人 Petrucelli
- he's pulling a fast one. - How so?
- 他在捣鬼 - 怎么会?
Turns out, rum ain't the only thing you're running.
事实是 你们捣鼓的不只是朗姆酒
Him and the other ones, Luciano and his partner--
他跟那个Luciano还有他的合伙人
Lansky.
叫Lansky
- Who's there? - McCoy.
- 谁在那儿? - McCoy
He's with me. Anyway...
他跟我一起 不管怎样...
turns out they're stashing heroin in with your hooch
原来他们用你的私酒夹藏毒品
and trucking it north.
用卡车运往北方
And you know this how?
你怎么知道的?
A girl has her ways.
姑娘自有门路
You tell anyone besides McCoy?
除了McCoy你还告诉别人了吗?
I prefer to live near the swamp, not in it.
我喜欢住沼泽边 而不是陷进去
- Well, keep him close by. - Do I have to?
- 那好 盯紧他 - 有必要吗?
Yes.
有
And, Sally, I owe you one.
还有 Sally 我欠你一次
And don't think I don't know it, sport.
别以为我不知道 朋友
From our wedding.
是婚礼上的
- Said how he's too old. - Aw.
- 说明他太老了 - 嗷
What are you doing here?
你来干嘛?
I like to know what my clients are insuring.
我想知道我客户都投什么保
- Keeps me inspired. - I understand you've bought a policy.
- 让我保持动力 - 我了解到你买了保险
Whole life.
终身寿险
When it matures, you'll be sitting on a nice little nest egg.
等它到期后 你会坐享一个漂亮的小金蛋
Let's hope it doesn't hatch.
但愿它不会孵化
Quite a boy you've got here.
你养了个好小子
Left college to take a position with the mayor's office?
大学辍学到市长办公室谋求席位?
That's what I call gumption.
这就是我说的魄力
- What is it you want exactly, Mr.-- - Balanchuk.
- 你到底想要什么 - 叫我Balanchuk
I recently transferred from the Chicago office.
我最近刚从芝加哥办公室调过来
Mr. Balanchuk.
Balanchuk先生
I just need to go over a few documents and I'll be out of your hair.
我只是要查看一些文件 然后就不打扰你们了
We'll move into the kitchen, give you some privacy.
我们移到厨房去 你们私下聊
You should thank your father.
你该感谢你父亲
He knows that in an instant,
他明白厄运
tragedy can strike and everything a man's worked for,
只在一瞬间 而人为的一切努力
everything he loves, everything he holds dear...
钟爱的一切 看重的一切...
...can be gone.
...转瞬即逝
- Get to work now, huh? - Yes, sir.
- 该上班了 嗯? - 是 先生
You come to my fuckin' house?
你跑来老子家里?
Joseph Balanchuk has been dead for two years.
Joseph Balanchuk死了两年了
John Torrio paid for his funeral.
John Torrio已经下葬
- They don't update me on turnover. - Playing me for a chump?
- 他们可不向我回报动向 - 把我当傻子玩?
You asked what I know. That's what I know.
你问我知道什么 我就知道这些
Next time, know better.
下一次 聪明点
Or as God is my judge, that bright-eyed young son of yours
不然老天作证 你那年少热情的儿子
will be breaking rocks up at Trenton.
就要沦落特伦顿了
- Everything okay? Yeah. - Just a spill.
- 都还好吗? - 嗯 是杯子洒了
That was some good coffee. Thank you.
咖啡很不错 谢谢你
Price still hasn't come in yet.
价格还没有出来
New York City
纽约市
Yes, please hold for Mrs. Rohan.
是 Rohan太太来电
Hello? Yes, this is she.
你好? 是 是我
I'm calling in regard to your advertisement in the "Herald."
我打电话是问您在"Herald"登的广告
The apartments in Inwood.
公寓是在Inwood
No, I am unmarried.
不 我未婚
Recently widowed, actually.
其实 是新寡
Isham Garden Apartments 2 room, 500
Isham花园公寓 2室 500美金
A personal tour would be grand.
能亲自参观真是太好了
And in terms of rent, is that--
说到租金 能不能...
I-- I'm sorry. I'll have to call you back.
抱歉 我再打给你
Changing your residence?
要搬家吗?
I-- just considering my options.
我...只是多个选择
Mr. Bennett is still at lunch.
Bennett先生还在吃午饭
May I get you something, Mr. Redstone?
您要点什么吗 Redstone先生?
- Have you any milk? - Certainly.
- 有牛奶吗? - 有
May I inquire as to your salary, Mrs. Rohan?
我能问问你薪水多少吗 Rohan太太?
$11 per week.
周薪11美金
With the occasional bonus for good performance.
表现好了偶尔还能拿笔奖金
That's $572 annually
年薪就是572美金了
with a prospective yearly rental of over half that.
预期年租金都超过半数年薪了
I imagine you're frugal,
我猜你勤俭节约
but subtracting for the grocer,
但是除去饮食
transportation, clothing, sundries and what have you,
交通 衣物 杂项开支等等
it seems these particular quarters are above your means.
看来这些单身公寓超乎你的承受能力啊
I fail to see what business this is of yours.
我看不出来这关你什么事
May I offer you some free advice?
我能给你一点免费的建议吗?
Is there anything more expensive in the world?
这世上还有更贵的东西吗?
Forget this place and call me.
别看这地方了 打电话给我
I own several buildings uptown.
我在上城区有几座大楼
Perhaps I could steer you
或许我能给你引荐一些
to more suitable accommodations.
更合适的住宅
CIrcle 6-4408
环形街 6-4408
In exchange for what?
以什么为交换?
Your boss, Mr. Bennett,
你老板 Bennett先生
he and his ilk are systematically driving down
他和他家族正有条不紊地压低
the price of Anaconda Realty stock,
Anaconda不动产的股价
in which I'm invested.
也就是我投资的股票
Soon, no doubt, they plan on buying it back.
毫无疑问 他们很快就会补进
I need to know when this happens.
我想知道具体时机
- I could lose my job. - Yes, you could.
- 我会失业的 - 不错 有可能
Or perhaps gain something better.
又或者挣点好的
Come on, Abe, quit flirting.
别介 Abe 别打情骂俏了
Hello, Robert.
你好 Robert
Nice chatting with you, Mrs. Rohan.
和你聊天很愉快 Rohan太太
Got something special coming in.
手上有些特别的
You're the first person I thought of.
我第一个就想到你
He show his face around here,
一旦他在附近现身
him or one of his boys, you get word to me right quick.
不管是他还是他手下 你们立马通知我
Ain't seen a hair of the doctor since the other night.
自从那晚以后 连一根博士毛也没见过
Ain't heard his speechifying neither.
也没听说他有演讲
His jabbering days be over soon enough.
他唧唧歪歪的日子就快到头了
Tonight we pay a visit down the Northside
今晚我们去北边走走
and see how he--
看他怎么...
Back in the kitchen, ofay. This here private.
回厨房去 白佬 这是私人地盘
So this here the new dishwasher Nucky hire?
这是Nucky新招的洗碗工?
Half-face white boy taking our jobs.
半边脸的白小子抢我们饭碗
Well, the way I see it,
我看到的是
one man got as much right to eat as another.
五脏庙前 人人平等
And this here man a friend of mine.
而这人是我一朋友
Mr. Harrow.
Harrow先生
Mr. White.
White先生
You need something, you look me up.
你要什么 就来找我
Tonight, over at UNIA.
今晚 在UNIA
We wait till after dark.
我们等到天黑以后
Ain't nobody gonna be there but Narcisse and his men.
除了Narcisse和他手下 不会有别人在
So he's running, being chased
所以他被追得一直跑
through these giant flowerpots,
穿过那些大花盆
and he's jumping and bouncing in and out
他蹦过来跳过去
like he's got springs in his shoes.
好像鞋里装了弹簧似的
What? Who was?
什么? 你说谁?
Douglas Fairbanks. Ain't you listening?
Douglas Fairbanks 你听着没?
Hey, Nuck,
嘿 Nuck
you see "The Thief of Bagdad"?
你看过"巴格达大盗"没?
You've got time to go to the pictures?
你有时间去电影院?
No.
没
Just, you know.
只不过 你懂的
I need you to take some men, head out to the White Horse Pike.
我要你带几个人 前往白马路
What's out there?
那边怎么了?
A convoy of trucks heading from Tampa to New York.
有一队卡车从塔帕开往纽约
- You want me to stop it? - Yes.
- 你要我拦住他们? - 嗯
And find the heroin Petrucelli's piggybacking with our rum.
搜出Petrucelli用咱们朗姆酒捎带的毒品
Petrucelli's in business with Masseria?
Petrucelli和Masseria做买卖?
Masseria, Luciano, Lansky.
Masseria和Luciano还有Lansky
- Jesus. - This kid, this fucking Luciano.
- 天 - 这嫩仔 大爷的Luciano
Should have let me plug him years ago when I had the chance.
几年前就该让我趁机崩了他
First, let's make sure it's true.
首先搞清楚是不是真的
- Bring Knox and a couple of his men. - Flash some tin, less likely to get messy.
- 带上Knox和他两个手下 - 把麻烦降到最低
Just get it done.
搞定就行
You take everything north of 22nd.
你接手22大道以北所有地盘
That's 84 speaks in total.
总共84个据点
Up to or including Madison?
包不包括麦迪逊街?
Include it.
包括
Let Hymie Weiss try and tell you otherwise.
不然就让Hymie Weiss告诉你
Johnny, hey. Thought you'd gone already.
Johnny 嘿 还以为你已经走了
- Who's this? - George.
- 这是谁? - George
From the flower shop. I told you about him, didn't I?
花店来的 我跟你提过他 是吧?
No.
没
Sir, he helped us arrange O'Banion's retirement party.
先生 他帮我们安排了O'Banion的退隐派对
No, that was a disgruntled customer. Half a fin for a dozen roses--
不 是某个怀恨的买家 两块五买一打玫瑰
you get 'em home, they're already wilting. Drive any fella to murder.
等到带回家 花儿都蔫了 换做是谁都会杀人
- George here's gonna be taking over my collections. - Yeah, I'm moving Ralphie up.
- George是来接手我的地盘 - 嗯 我要提升Ralphie
Oh, you are?
噢 是吗?
So's I can run the distribution more hands-on.
那我就能腾出手来掌控大局
And what'll I be doing?
那我做什么?
Come again?
再说一次?
While your hands are on the distribution, what will I be doing?
你腾出手做布局的时候 我做什么?
Whatever you want. I mean, I ain't gonna squeeze you out or nothing.
想干嘛干嘛 我说 我又不是要把你排挤出局
You wouldn't squeeze me out of my own operation?
你不会把我挤出我自己的生意?
- That is very generous of you. - You know what I mean.
- 你可真大方 - 你知道我的意思
I mean, I know you like to relax.
我是说 我知道你喜欢休息
I got people coming up behind me.
我这里后浪推前浪
They're, what do you call it, ambitious.
他们个个 你怎么说来着 雄心勃勃
- I've been meaning to talk to you about this anyway. - So talk.
- 我一直想和你说说来着 - 那就说
We had discussions, you and me, about the future
我们讨论过 就你和我 探讨过你从意大利
when you got back from Italy.
回来以后的事
Expanding my role when you retire.
等你退休后扩张我的势力
But I ain't retiring, Al.
可我没退休 Al
No. Right.
当然 不错
Of course.
必须的
I know that.
我知道
Someday. Eventually.
到最后 总有一天
I'm gonna go. It's good you're thinking ahead.
我要走了 你深谋远虑是好事
I remind you all once again that our other business must be kept far away--
我再提醒你们一次 我们其他生意必须远离...
Doctor.
博士
Watch out!
小心
Get down! Get down!
趴下! 趴下!
Come on, let's go.
好了 我们走
Chalky--
Chalky...
Go! Go!
快走! 快走!
C. Auguste Dupin.
C.Auguste Dupin
I don't know him.
我不认识他
He's fictional. A detective.
他是虚构的 是个警探
"The Murders in the Rue Morgue."
出自"莫格街凶杀案"
Right.
是了
Those stories are the reason I wanted to join law enforcement.
那些故事就是我想加入执法机关的动机
You've handled yourself well.
你把自己控制得很好
I'm sure you were a good cop.
我相信你曾是个好警察
Are we friends now?
我们现在成朋友了?
Dinner bell.
开饭锣
You don't have to be my pal, Eli.
你没必要和我交朋友 Eli
I mean, heck, I don't even think you like me.
我是说 见鬼 我觉得你甚至都不喜欢我
But really, this doesn't have to be so bad.
可真的也没必要闹这么僵
Okay, fellas.
来了 伙计们
- Fan it out. Let's go. - All right.
- 散开走 我们上 - 好
Hold up.
留步
Stay where you are, sir.
原地待命 各位
Eli, what the fuck is this?
Eli 这是搞什么?
- Search the trucks. - Move!
- 搜车 - 快!
Since when did you start riding with the help?
你什么时候开始跟这些佣人同行了?
You want to tell me what's transpiring here? We're already behind.
你不告诉我这怎么回事? 我们已经晚点了
- It's none of your business what we got in there. - Is there a problem, Agent Selby?
- 我们里面有什么不关你的事 - 有问题吗 Selby警探?
This wise head won't get out of the way.
这机灵鬼不让道
Perhaps you're using the wrong approach.
也许是你用的方法不对
Step aside, please. Tell it to Joe the boss.
- 请让开 - 跟老板Joe说去
Why don't you relay the message instead?
不如由你去转达吧?
Any other objections?
还有人反对吗?
- No, sir. No, sir. - All right, all right. All right.
- 没了 长官 没有 长官 - 好吧 好 好
Open up. Open up.
打开 打开
Was that necessary?
有必要吗?
You heard the man. They're already behind.
你也听见了 人家已经晚点了
Take your time, by all means.
不管怎样 慢慢来
And before this gets any further out of hand, please tell me how I can be of assistance.
在场面失控以前 请告诉我该如何配合
We understand you're carrying more than rum.
我们得知你们运送的不只是朗姆酒
If we are, that's beyond any personal knowledge I have of the situation.
就算是 我个人对此事也是一无所知
Dr. Narcisse.
Narcisse博士
- Chalky White. - I told him he wasn't here, boss.
- Chalky White - 我跟他说了人不在 老板
You don't tell Dr. Narcisse anything.
轮不到你跟Narcisse博士说什么
He's not.
他不在
Now you've heard it from me, so...
现在你听到我说了 那么...
He came at me. I want him dead.
他偷袭我 我要他死
- Came at you how? - With a pistol.
- 怎么偷袭你? - 用手枪
He and his men killed three of mine.
他和他手下杀了我三个人
- This happened tonight? - And tonight it ends.
- 今晚发生的事? - 今晚就得了结
What you yourself began.
你自己招惹的
Dead!
要他死!
I will cut him from nave to chaps.
我要把他切成肉酱
You'll find the meat tough, Doctor.
你会发现那是块滚刀肉 博士
Tell me where he is or don't.
我要他的下落 说还是不说
Your choice.
你自己选
Dr. Narcisse,
Narcisse博士
there's something I've been meaning to ask you
有件事我一直想问你
for quite some time.
忍了很久
Who the fuck do you think you are?
尼玛你以为你算老几?
Cast your lot? Is it so?
有你一份 是不是?
Your leaving on your feet or on your back is entirely up to you.
要走着出去还是横着出去 完全取决于你
So don't make a mistake.
别犯错
- You ready for this? - Just say.
- 你准备好了? - 一句话
I'll put one in this burrhead right now.
我立马赏这毛刺头吃枪子
Mr. Thompson, he not ready for this.
Thompson先生 他还没准备好
Don't be so sure.
别这么肯定
I told you, I don't know where Chalky is.
我跟你说了 我不知道Chalky在哪儿
You've got problems with him, take it up with him.
你跟他有干戈 就找他解决
Now get the fuck out of my club.
现在 滚出我的俱乐部
When I run him through, watch the light go out,
等我杀了他 看着他活生生消逝
I hope he knows what a friend he had in you.
我希望他知道他交了你这么个朋友
You sure this copacetic?
你确定这样好吗?
- I ain't never fought no war but my own. - They're painting the Legion hall.
- 我也不是没干过孤军作战的事 - 他们在粉刷军团大厅
You'll be safe here through the weekend.
整个周末你在这儿都没事
Went straight through.
子弹穿透而出
How you know that?
你怎么知道?
I've been around many people who've been shot.
我周边很多人挨过枪子儿
It's your friend.
是你朋友
Oh, my God. What did he do?
噢 天 他干了什么?
Brought her directly, Mr. White.
直接带她过来的 White先生
Ain't nobody follow y'all?
没人跟踪你们吗?
You go on now. Make the midnight show so they ain't suspicious.
你马上回去 准备夜场秀 这样他们不会起疑
- Yes, sir. - You go, too.
- 是 先生 - 你也去吧
I'll be fine.
我没事的
He'll come after you, you know.
你知道 他会死咬着你的
Come after us. Let him come.
- 死咬着我们 - 让他来
Can you even raise your arm?
你还能举起胳膊吗?
Brooklyn
布鲁克林
You come to me practically begging, some wet-behind-the-ears little shit.
你来就是求我 可笑的破事
- Nucky-- - You assure me your intentions are honorable,
- Nucky... - 你向我保证过你的意图体面
that you and your partner have big plans for the future.
你和你的合作伙伴在未来有大计划
- If you'd just let me speak-- - I let you in on the deal.
- 如果你允许我说... - 我让你加入
Things are going great and what do you do the second you get the chance?
所有的事情都进展顺利 得到这机会后你干了什么?
- Mr. Thompson-- - You stick it up my fucking ass.
- Thompson先生... - 你他妈捅了我一刀
We were coerced, Charlie and I.
我们是被逼的 Charlie和我
By Masseria.
Masseria逼的
- He found out about Tampa from his cousin... - Petrucelli.
- 他从他堂兄那得知了坦帕的事情... - Petrucelli
...then realized he could use it to his advantage.
然后想到可以用它来替自己牟利
- As did you and your greaseball partner. - He would have killed us if we didn't go along.
- 就像你和你的意大利伙伴一样 - 如果我们不听话他就会杀了我们
You think I fucking won't?
你认为我他妈的就不会?
I know that is a distinct possibility, though I do pray to God it doesn't happen.
我知道那很有可能 尽管我向上帝祈祷那不会发生
If it were strictly up to me, sir, I'd have nothing to do with narcotics.
如果只是我的话 先生 我不会沾上毒品
There is plenty of money in liquor, which is a much safer
酒的生意很赚钱
and eminently more socially acceptable--
它更安全也更容易被社会接受
You've got two seconds to drop the fucking Boy Scout routine or you're going in that hole.
你有两秒钟来放弃你他妈童子军那一套 要么你就滚进那个坑
There's a fortune to be made in heroin.
海洛因能发大财
Millions and millions of dollars.
很多很多的钱
Now I don't know about you,
我不知道你
but the way I saw it, it was the same life I was risking either way.
但我的想法是 无论哪条路我都一样要冒风险
I'm begging you, Mr. Thompson. Please.
我在求您 Thompson先生 求您
What would you have done if you were me?
如果您是我您会做什么?
- You're going to call him. - Call who?
- 你会打电话给他 - 给谁?
Masseria. If he'd like to see you
Masseria 如果他想再见到你
or his heroin ever again,
或者他的海洛因
tell him to get his ass down here.
叫他滚过来
Chalky White left a message. Says it's urgent.
Chalky White留了言 说很急
You're set for 2:00 with the Palm Court. Mr. Murphy is running five minutes late.
2点您和Palm法院有约 Murphy先生会迟到五分钟
Remind me to stick it to him later.
提醒我过后记得惩罚他
And do me a favor.
帮我个忙
Make sure these trade confirmations get filed.
确认将这些交易凭条归档
Anaconda Realty?
Anaconda不动产?
Redstone, some of these other dubs, they're down by 80%.
Redstone 还有一些其他的傻子 他们跌了有百分之八十
I'll tell you, they say these kikes are smart.
我告诉你 他们说犹太佬很聪明
Well, this one's dumb as a doornail with the deepest pockets I've ever seen.
哦 这个比门钉还蠢的家伙是我见过最有钱的
- They're no match for you, sir. - They're greedy, every last one of them.
- 他们比不上您 先生 - 他们很贪婪 每一个都是
Redstone included.
也包括Redstone
Thinks he can get rich without doing a thing.
想想 他不用做任何事就能变得富有
Well, the more fool him.
那么 他更蠢了
I'd like to take the new Duesenberg for a test drive.
我想去试驾那辆新的Duesenberg
There's a number for a salesman on my desk somewhere.
我桌上的什么地方有一个销售员的号码
Consider it done.
包在我身上
That's what Valentino drives, you know.
那就是Valentino开的车 你知道的
It's warm, but it's all I can find.
温的 但这是我唯一能找到的
- They keep the rest locked up. - It's fine, thank you.
- 他们把剩下都锁上了 - 够了 谢谢
How we get to Narcisse?
我们要怎么对付Narcisse?
May we have some privacy, please?
请问我们能单独呆会吗?
Of course.
当然
Are you thinking straight about any of this?
这事上你头脑还清醒吧?
She put the knife in Purnsley back.
她把刀子捅进了Purnsley的背
He came to see me last night. Narcisse.
昨晚他来找我了 Narcisse
- What he offer? - It doesn't matter.
- 他给了你什么? - 那无关紧要
But what he wants is you on a slab.
但他要你死
What you want?
你要什么?
I can tell you what I don't want, and that's a fucking war.
我能告诉你我不想要什么 那就是他妈的战争
You okay?
你还好吧?
Been worse.
更糟了
You've been better, too.
你也已经好多了
So push come to shove,
所以情势更紧急了
what happen then?
然后呢?
I'm here, aren't I?
我在这了 不是吗?
You said you ain't want no war.
你说了你不想要战争
I don't want the trots either, but when I get them, I deal with it.
我也不想要鳟鱼 但逮到它们的时候 我就会处理
You know, someone once told me all of man's problems come from his inability
有人曾经告诉我 所有男人的问题都是因为
to just sit in a room.
他不能老实地呆在房间里
Doing that right now.
现在正在那么做
Then I suppose your troubles are over.
那么我想你的麻烦已经结束了
Don't do anything until you hear from me.
在听到我的消息前 什么也不要做
...and as a devoted friend
作为善良又高贵的
of the good and decent people of the Northside,
北城人民的忠诚朋友
I vow this--
我宣誓
neither I nor the members of the sheriff's department
不论是我还是任何一个警察
will rest until every last one of the cowardly perpetrators
在抓住所有这次恶劣袭击事件的
of this heinous attack are brought to justice.
暴徒之前 我们绝不会停下脚步
Thank you.
谢谢
Mr. Mayor, is it true
市长先生
Chalky White is being sought for questioning?
你们正在搜捕Chalky White去问讯是真的吗?
Mr. Mayor, will the city rebuild the UNIA office?
市长先生 市政府会重建UNIA办公室吗?
- Harry, help me with this lamp. - All right, got it.
- Harry 帮我弄一下这个灯 - 好 知道了
Ah, Nucky Thompson.
啊 Nucky Thompson
Always a pleasure.
荣幸之至
Perhaps for you.
或许是因为你
Things look different during the day, no?
这里在白天看上去不太一样 不是吗?
You see all the-- how you say?
你看到了一切 你怎么说?
The flaws.
缺点
I've always preferred bringing things to light.
我总是喜欢把东西暴露在光下
Meyer, now why you so blue?
Meyer 你为什么这么忧郁?
It could have something to do with the heroin you had him import.
可能和你让他进口的海洛因有关
Ah, si. He mention this to me when he called.
啊 这样 他打给我的时候提到了
So what do you have to say for yourself?
那你要为自己辩护些什么吗?
We wait, huh?
我们等等 嗯?
???
直到我的合作伙伴到达
What partner?
什么伙伴?
Forgive me my tardiness.
请原谅我迟到了
It is a quality I deplore in others.
这是被我谴责的品性
Ah, no. We just get started.
啊 不 我们刚开始
What the hell is going on?
究竟发生了什么?
The world is going on, Mr. Thompson.
没有你地球依旧在转 Thompson先生
Without you, depending on what passes here today.
取决于今天这里通过的东西
- You two are partners? - In a manner of speaking, yes.
- 你们是合作伙伴? - 在某种意义上 是的
As you've deduced, I am deeply entrenched in the business of providing heroin
正如你推测的那样 我执着于卖海洛因
to those wretched souls who desire it.
给那些渴望它的可悲灵魂的生意
Mr. Masseria and I have recently embarked on an arrangement
最近Masseria先生和我开始了一项合作
wherein he will supply me with product via Tampa.
他会从坦帕给我供货
Using my trucks for delivery.
用我的卡车运送
- So you see. - We do business already, the three of us.
- 你看到了 - 我们已经合作了 我们三个
And if I don't like it?
如果我不喜欢?
I should paint you a picture, but I assure you it would not be pretty.
我应该给你画张像 但我保证那不会好看
There is money to be made, Mr. Thompson.
有钱赚 Thompson先生
A very great deal of it.
非常多的钱
I will not be your friend, but I will be an able partner.
我不会成为你的朋友 但我会是个很有能力的合作伙伴
One far more dependable than you've ever had before.
一个比你之前所有合作伙伴都要可靠的伙伴
- Just like that? - No.
- 就那样? - 不
I will require your full support on the Northside
我要求你在北城的全力支持
to include you delivering your Mr. White to me personally.
包括将你的White先生送到我这里来 私人要求
- This is nonnegotiable. - What do I get?
- 这没有商量的余地 - 那我会得到什么?
What do you want?
你要什么?
For starters, I want my fucking share.
首先 我要我他妈的份额
One third of any heroin already imported.
三分之一已经进口的海洛因
And one third of any imported in the future.
未来要进口的三分之一
So we have struck a bargain, then?
那么我们达成一致了 然后?
Yes.
是的
You will not be sorry, Mr. Thompson.
你不会后悔的 Thompson先生
I see great days ahead.
我看到了光明的未来
The mayor will be right with you, Mr. Thompson.
市长马上就来 Thompson先生
- Anything from Knox? - Can't find him.
- Knox那有什么消息吗? - 找不到他
Please hold for Mayor Bader.
请等待Bader市长的应答
- Hello? - Ed, it's me.
- 喂? - Ed 是我
- Nucky. - Listen to me clearly.
- Nucky - 仔细听我说
This is an emergency.
紧急事件
I need you to send two sheriff's deputies to get Chalky White out of town.
我需要你派两个警员送Chalky White出城
Okay.
好
Fella goes to a drugstore to buy rubbers.
Fella去药店买避孕套
The guy goes, "You want a bag with that?"
那人说 "你要一袋那个吗?"
Fella says, "No, thanks, she ain't that ugly."
Fella说 "不 谢谢 她没那么丑"
How do you make your wife scream while you're having sex?
你们上床的时候 怎么让你的妻子尖叫?
Call her, tell her about it.
打电话给她 告诉她这件事
All right.
好了
All right, I'm heading out.
好了 我出去了
Johnny, stay. Have a drink.
Johnny 留下来 喝一杯
I'll catch your matinee performance tomorrow.
明天我会赶上你的日场演出的
Another round.
再来一轮
- What's that called? - Tom Collins.
- 那叫什么? - Tom Collins
- I'll kill that bum. - Oh.
- 我会杀了那懒鬼 - 哦
What's a good bar and a good woman have in common?
好酒吧和好女人有什么共同点?
I don't know.
我不知道
Liquor in the front, poker in the back.
前面是酒 后面是牌 (先口交后肛交)
- You've never--? - Al, you got a call.
- 你从来没...? - Al 你有电话
Who is it?
谁?
- He didn't say. - Take a message.
- 他没说 - 让他留言
Said it's important.
说很重要
I'll take it in there. Come on.
我在那接 来
- Hello. - This Al?
- 喂 - 是Al?
Yeah, who's this?
是 你是谁?
- Never mind who it is. - Yeah? Then what the fuck do you want?
- 别管我是谁 - 嗯? 那你他妈要干嘛?
Nothing. I was just calling to say good-bye.
没什么 只是打电话来说再见
Down! Get down!
趴下! 趴下!
Ralph! Ralphie!
Ralph! Ralphie!
You okay?
你还好吧?
I'm all right.
我没事
Oh, my God!
哦 天哪!
Sweet, merciful Jesus. Oh, my God.
亲爱的 慈悲的耶稣 哦 天哪
Come on, come on.
过来 过来
Well, lucky for John he left when he did, huh?
呃 John真好运 离开了才发生 不是吗?
You okay?
你还好吧?
Are you sure I can't offer you something else?
你确定我没法给你别的?
I'm fine, thank you. Please.
我没事 谢谢 请
I'm too nervous to eat.
我太紧张了以至于吃不下
You needn't worry. I'm a married man.
你不用担心 我是个已婚男人
You must be joking.
你在开玩笑
I am.
我是
Though what would Mr. Thompson think?
不过Thompson先生会怎么想?
He can think what he wants.
他可以想他要什么
My life is my own.
我的生活是自己的
Not that this is that. This is business.
不是这个就是那个 这是交易
Drink your tea. It settles the nerves.
喝你的茶 它能舒缓神经
It's impossible to get ahead.
要进步那不可能
And believe me, I've tried.
相信我 我试过了
I work hard, I save my--
我努力工作 我存...
You owe no one any explanations, Miss Rohan.
你不欠任何人解释 Rohan小姐
Mr. Bennett--
Bennett先生
Mr. Bennett is a criminal no different than--
Bennett先生也是个罪犯 和...
Than me?
和我一样?
I was going to say my husband.
我本来要说我的丈夫
Though to be fair, one could paint me with that same brush.
不过为了公平 也可以用那个来说我
Anaconda Realty. Mr. Bennett and his partners own the company.
Anaconda不动产 Bennett先生和他的合作伙伴共同拥有那家公司
He bought more shares this afternoon.
今天下午他买了更多的股票
You should do so yourself as soon as possible.
你也应该尽快买进
30,000 shares preferred stock. You shouldn't sell until he does.
- 三万股优先股 - 在他抛掉之前你都不要卖掉
I'll let you know when that happens.
那个时候我会让你知道
In return for what?
交换条件?
A rent-free apartment guaranteed for five years.
五年免租金的公寓
A safe neighborhood with rooms for the children.
安全的社区 还有给孩子活动的空间
You'll accept nothing from Mr. Thompson, yet you will from me?
你不要Thompson先生的任何东西 而从我这要?
I earned this.
这是我赚来的
And when it's over, I owe you nothing.
所以当它结束的时候 我不欠你任何东西
We have a deal.
成交
Very well.
很好
I've never done business with a woman before.
我从未和女人做过交易
Well, how did you like it?
哦 那么你喜欢吗?
Quite the treat.
挺不错
You got peoples anywhere?
你在哪里有人?
Just here in this room.
只有这里 在这间屋子里
You?
你?
You stay here, wait till morning.
你留在这 直到早上
Catch a train out west. You'll be safe there.
登上去西部的火车 在那你会很安全
I'm going wherever you go.
你去哪我就去哪
They're here.
他们来了
Mr. White? Climb in the back.
White先生? 从后面上来
Crouch down a little.
弯点腰
Uncle Nucky.
Nucky伯父
Will, what are you doing here?
Will 你在这干什么?
I tried to call. The line was busy.
我打过电话 占线
Want a drink?
要来一杯吗?
What's wrong?
怎么了?
Earlier today the mayor gave a press conference.
今天早些时候市长召开了新闻发布会
- I saw the afternoon paper. - Well, afterwards he had a meeting.
- 我看了下午的报纸 - 嗯 然后他开了个会
This colored doctor from the Northside.
北城来的黑人博士
- Narcisse? - I don't know.
- Narcisse? - 我不知道
He had a beard. Suit cost more than--
他有胡子 西服价值比...
- What did they talk about? - I couldn't hear,
- 他们说了什么? - 我听不到
but they were in Bader's office for over an hour.
但是他们在Bader的办公室里呆了一个多小时
Get me the American Legion Hall on Pacific.
给我接Pacifica的军团大厅
Thought we was going to Philly.
我以为我们要去费城
We are. Like I said.
是的 就像我说的那样
Missed the turnoff back there.
刚刚错过了那个岔道
That right?
是吗?
Doing some work on that road.
道路施工
Taking a different route.
走的是另一条路
- You all right? - Yeah. Shoulder.
- 你还好吧? - 嗯 肩膀
Hurt a touch.
有点疼
You'll feel better with some sleep.
睡一会你会好过点
Maybe I'll close my eyes a while.
也许我眯一下
No!
不!
Oh, damn!
哦 该死的!
Steer the car!
控制好车!
Help me get him out.
帮我把他弄出去
Carnegie Hall, one month ago.
卡耐基音乐厅 一个月以前
Nearly 3,000 Negroes in attendance to see Garvey.
将近三千黑人出席去看Garvey (Marcus Garvey 黑星的领导人)
(Marcus Garvey President of the Black Star) If anything, his arrest has made him more popular.
如果可能 他被捕会让他更出名
Man to his left, that Patterson?
他左边的人 是Patterson?
Yes, sir.
是的 先生
- We can't get any more inside than him. - Pathetic, isn't it?
- 我们无法比他更深入 - 真可悲 不是吗?
They join his club, attend his mandatory outings.
他们加入他的俱乐部 出席他规定的室外集会
In exchange, he sells them uniforms signifying nothing,
作为交换 他卖给他们没有任何意义的制服
with the profits being used to fund his appeal.
得到的收入被用于支持他的申诉
That man has done more damage free on bail than most criminals achieve in a lifetime.
那个男人做到了很多罪犯穷极一生 都做不到的破坏 还逍遥自在
3,000 Negroes with ideas in their heads--
三千个有自己想法的黑鬼
that's a threat worth worrying about.
那是个值得注意的威胁
Your tail's wagging, Jim.
你很兴奋 Jim
I got our weak link.
我找到了那个弱点
Nucky Thompson-- his brother Eli.
Nucky Thompson 他的弟弟Eli
We backed him into a corner.
我们把他逼到了角落
- He's going to connect all the dots for us, Edgar. - Our man in Harlem.
- 他会为我们将所有的线索串起来 Edgar - 我们黑人区的人
I may need you from time to time to nourish that relationship.
我可能会需要你不时地来维持这关系
Yes, Mr. Director.
是 长官
What is this?
这是什么意思?
I'm late for a debriefing.
我汇报要迟到了
Yes, of course, sir.
是的 当然 长官
Since when are you so shy?
你从什么时候开始这么害羞的?
This isn't the right place to be.
这里不是合适的地方
Do you just want to sit at home moping?
你就想坐在家里 拖地?
What do you have to be so happy about?
什么事让你那么高兴?
Tonight? Nothing at all.
今晚? 什么也没有
- That's why we're here. - Boardwalk Slim.
- 那就是我们在这里的原因 - Boardwalk滑步
We just commencing.
我们刚开始
Sit anywhere you want.
随意坐
We're allowed to?
可以吗?
After hours.
非营业时间
It's all just us here.
这里只有我们
Go on. That's what you came here for.
继续 那就是你来这的原因
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Just lying down for a minute.
只是想躺下休息一会
No need to apologize. It's an intoxicating brew--
不需要道歉 这是令人迷醉的交融
the music, the smoke, the alcohol.
音乐 烟 酒
I haven't had anything.
我什么都没有沾
What's stopping you?
是什么阻止了你?
Not in the mood, I suppose.
我想是没心情吧
At times, it seems all there is
有时 似乎只剩下我们
is us and our unhappiness.
和我们的不愉快
This is one of those times.
这就是其中一次
Sit. Please.
请坐
- You're not with the musicians. - No.
- 你不是和乐队一起的 - 不是
I came with my brother.
我和我兄弟一起来的
That's him playing with Mr. Coates.
和Coates先生一起演奏的就是他
You are Mr. White's child?
你是White先生的孩子?
You know him?
你认识他?
We are intimately associated.
我们私下关系很好
Richard Pastor.
Richard牧师
Maybelle White.
Maybelle White
- No wonder he's so proud. - Do you know where he is?
- 我一点都不怀疑他会那么骄傲 - 你知道他在哪吗?
Alas, no.
唉 不
I've heard the rumors,
我听到了很多谣言
the lies.
还有谎言
And beneath it all, the old drumbeat of injustice.
而在这一切的背后 是不义的古老鼓点
Mother won't even get out of bed.
母亲甚至不会起床
And you are to be married, are you not?
你要结婚了 不是吗?
Not as of 3:00 this afternoon. Samuel wasn't even there.
今天下午三点以后就不是了 Samuel甚至都不在那儿
His father told me. I think he enjoyed it.
他父亲告诉了我 我想他很喜欢那样
Why must it be the daughters who suffer?
为什么要让他的女儿来承受痛苦?
That's the funny thing. I'm not suffering.
这就是有意思的地方了 我不痛苦
I'm--
我...
I don't know what I am.
我不知道我是什么
Except something I'm not supposed to be.
除了我不该是的部分
Dangerous...
危险...
for people like us.
对我们这样的人来说
Like us?
我们这样的?
To be what we are, where we are,
坚持本我 听随本心
and dare to stand free,
不惧自由站立
what could be more lonely?
还有什么比这更孤独的事情吗?
I was supposed to come here to forget things.
我来是想忘记的
Then go
那么去
and forget.
然后忘记
What the fuck's going on? You've got the Seventh Regiment out there.
他妈的究竟发生了什么? 你把第七团都召到外面了
Bader's turned. He's in Narcisse's pocket.
Bader反水了 他投靠了Narcisse
- What? - You reach anyone yet?
- 什么? - 你联系人了吗?
He's locked inside his office preparing a statement.
他把自己锁在办公室里准备声明
Word is two deputies are dead on the Pike.
有两个警员死在了Pike路上
- Why are you here? - He's doing his job, Eli.
- 你为什么在这? - 他在做他的工作 Eli
Why else would I put him next to Bader?
要不我为什么要把他放在Bader身边?
You need to leave this room.
你得离开这间屋子
He's already heard it all.
他已经听到所有的事情了
This is the life you want?
这就是你要的生活?
Pop, isn't it what we do?
爸 我们不就是这样的吗?
All right.
好
Let's get it sorted out.
让我们来弄清楚吧
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入